Some of your colleagues, and we talked about what's happened at the protests this week,
have called the president genocide, Joe.
Some of your colleagues have accused the president of supporting genocide, including Rashida Tlaib.
Do you agree with that word, genocide, that the president's been supporting a genocide, or does that go too far?
I think what we are seeing right now throughout the country
is that young people are appalled at the violence and the indiscriminate loss of life.
We are not just seeing 25,000 people that have died in Gaza.
We are seeing the starvation of millions of people, the displacement of over 2 million Gazans.
We have South Africa that has mounted a court in the ICJ.
The ICJ ruled this week that Israel has a grave responsibility to prevent genocide.
But they're still determining whether it's a genocide.
Do you think that term is responsible given that it's still under investigation?
I believe that they're still determining it.
But in the interim ruling, the fact that they said there's a responsibility to prevent it,
the fact that this word is even in play, the fact that this word is even in our discourse,
I think demonstrates the mass inhumanity that Gazans are facing.
And so whether you are an individual that believes this is a genocide, which, by the way,
is that it's still in prison, it's not a genocide, but often reforestation,
because there are no foreign language, and there are no foreign language,
which is why we are more and more, you know,
than others, the fact that this word is in the same way,
which is inappropriate for this situation,
which其實 becomes a problem for the right to the right to the right to the right.
So I guess that it could have been the most part of the divorce,
which is why we're still doing some kind of a society,
so it's trying to be the most part of the situation.
So as always, as always, it's a relationship,
which is the most part of the family,
so if you're not themselves doing a thing,